我沒有理由沮喪
I have no reason to frown
我不需要轉過身
I don't need to turn around
現在哭還有何用
What's the use in crying now
我不敢相信所見
I can't believe my eyes
我撒了一個瞞天大謊
I told myself the perfect lie
但我現在已不想死掉
But I don't feel like dying now
即使我給自己安排
最厄的運
And even though I turned the odds
against myself
我發現我又再次被
他人所救
Again I find that I've been saved
by someone else
所以今晚，我會改過重來
So tonight, I will make it right
我仍不懂為何
我會想要獨自吞淚
Still I don't know why
I thought I'd swallow all my tears
一直以來，我都想得太歪
All along, I was thinking wrong
我花太久搞清
我所需就在這
It took me far too long to see that
all I need's right here
我所需就在這
All I need's right here
有人說我瘋狂
Some say I lost my mind
至少我終於學會了
at least I found it given time
我再也不這樣脆弱
I won't go down so easily
對啦，我知道很明顯
Yeah, it's easy enough to admit
我本來就是不適合
it never was a perfect fit
那月球還是太小了
The moon is just too small for me
所以今晚，我會改過重來
So tonight, I will make it right
我仍不懂為何
我會想要獨自吞淚
Still I don't know why
I thought I'd swallow all my tears
一直以來，我都想得太歪
All along, I was thinking wrong
我花太久搞清
我所需就在這
It took me far too long to see that
all I need's right here
我所需就在這
All I need's right here
所以今晚，我會改過重來
So tonight, I will make it right
我仍不懂為何
我會想要獨自吞淚
Still I don't know why
I thought I'd swallow all my tears
所以今晚，我會改過重來
So tonight, I will make it right
我仍不懂為何
我會想要獨自吞淚
Still I don't know why
I thought I'd swallow all my tears
一直以來，我都想得太歪
All along, I was thinking wrong
我花太久搞清
我所需就在這
It took me far too long to see that
all I need's right here
我所需就在這
All I need's right here